timescity.com 2014-12-13

# TimesCity | Privacy Policy

TimesCity is part of Times Internet Ltd, (TIL), a company incorporated under the provisions of Indian Companies Act, 1996 and a wholly owned subsidiary of Bennett Coleman & Co. Limited.  
TIL respects the privacy of it's users and is committed to protect it in all respects. With a view to offer most enriching and holistic internet experience to it's users TIL offers a vast repository of Online Sites and variety of community services. You may read ['About Us'](http://www.indiatimes.com/aboutus/) to know more about timescity.com. Most of the Online Community Services are offered for free but you need a Universal mandatory registration to surf 'Indiatimes Channels' in detail. The information about the user as collected by TIL is: (a) information supplied by users and (b) information automatically tracked while navigation (Information).  
By using TIL's website or its services, you consent to collection, storage, and use of the personal information you provide (including any changes thereto as provided by you) for any of the services that we offer.   

## Use of Service

By using TimesCity, you warrant and represent that you are legally entitled to do so and to make use of your information provided across our products. Such information are collected during the Sign Up process namely - a) your name, b) email address, c) sex, d) age, e) password etc. The information supplies by users enable us to improve our sites and provide you the most user-friendly experience.  
All required information is service dependent and TIL may use the above said User information to, maintain, protect, and improve its services (including advertising services) and for developing new services. Such information will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and accessible in the public domain or is furnished under the Right to Information Act, 2005 or any other law for the time being in force.  

## Cookies

To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our users, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply (an example of this is when you ask for our Personalised Horoscope). A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control.  
Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors come. 

## Link to Third Party Sites

TIL includes links to other websites. Such sites are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site directly for more information.  
When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site. When you register with TIL, we contact you from time to time about updation of your content to provide the users such features that we believe may benefit you. 

## Information Sharing

TIL shares the sensitive personal information to any third party without obtaining the prior consent of the User in the following limited circumstances:

  * When it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms; for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.
  * TIL proposes to share such information within its group companies and officers and employees of such group companies for the purpose of processing personal information on its behalf. We also ensure that these recipients of such information agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

## Sharing of Personal Information

TimesCity is designed to help you find the best of restaurants, nightlife, events and movies around you and your city. In order to do this, TimesCity requires the use of such information including, but not limited to, your email, password and or other informations that was used while Signing Up with the services. TimesCity offers Sign Up process with our own sign up system and other platforms such as Facebook and Google+.  
TimesCity uses Facebook Connect and Google+ platforms as a medium for signing up only. The user data collected by TimesCity shall only be through the above mediums which will be be provided by the intended user through their Facebook or Google+ profile, no other data shall be collected/used by TimesCity apart from those that was permitted during Sign Up process.  
However, kindly note that the manner in which Facebook and Google+ uses, stores and discloses your information is governed solely by its policies, and TimesCity bears no liabilities/responsibility for its privacy practices and/or other actions of any third party site or service that may be enabled within the Service. 

## Use of Profile Data

We may use the personal information to provide the services you request. However, to the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will also provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. The personal information shall be used by us to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help/promote a safe service; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. In our efforts to continually improve our products and services, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our mobile application.   
We may occasionally ask you to engage in factual or interest based surveys. These surveys may ask you for more information around your interest and demographic information (like movies of choice, or prefered cuisines). The data so collected through surveys is solely to enhance your experience in the usage of the mobile application, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in, and to display content according to your preferences. It is however clarified that, filling in of such surveys is optional. 

## Location Sharing

TimesCity is about recommending you places around you and your city and in order to do that we would need to know your location. Whenever you open and interact with TimesCity app or visit timescity.com on your mobile, we use the location information from your mobile device or browser (latitude and longitude) to customize the experience around your location (i.e., showing you recommended places to eat, club or watch a movie nearby). Your location information is NEVER shared with others. TimesCity mobile app also allows you to select a locality of your choice or let the app determine your current location by tapping on your location name on Location Change screen. It allows us to tell you where the recommendations are based on the location that is determined by the device or your selection.

## Accessing And Updating Personal Information

When you use TIL's websites, we make good faith efforts to provide you, as and when requested by you, with access to your personal information and shall further ensure that any personal information or sensitive personal data or information found to be inaccurate or deficient shall be corrected or amended as feasible, subject to any requirement for such personal information or sensitive personal data or information to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems. 

## Prohibited Activities

You shall not host, display, upload, modify, publish, transmit, update or share any information on the Site, that -

  * belongs to another person and to which you do not have any right to.
  * is grossly harmful, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, paedophilic, libellous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically objectionable, disparaging, relating or encouraging money laundering or gambling, or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatever.
  * harm minors in any way.
  * infringes any patent, trademark, copyright or other proprietary rights.
  * violates any law for the time being in force.
  * deceives or misleads the addressee about the origin of such messages or communicates any information which is grossly offensive or menacing in nature.
  * impersonate another person.
  * contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer resource.
  * threatens the unity, integrity, defence, security or sovereignty of India, friendly relations with foreign states, or public order or causes incitement to the commission of any cognisable offence or prevents investigation of any offence or is insulting any other nation.

Any Content uploaded by you shall be subject to relevant laws and may disabled, or and may be subject to investigation under appropriate laws. Furthermore, if you are found to be in non-compliance with the laws and regulations, these terms, or the privacy policy of the Site, we may terminate your account/block your access to the Site and we reserve the right to remove any non-compliant Content uploaded by you.

## Notice of Copyright Infringement

TIL is not liable for any infringement of copyright arising out of materials posted on or transmitted through the site, or items advertised on the site, by end users or any other third parties. In the event you have any grievance relating to the processing of information provided by you, you may contact our Grievance Officer, at [copyright.infringement@indiatimes.com](mailto:copyright.infringement@indiatimes.com); or write at the following address  

> J B Sanchita  
>  Grievance Redressal Officer  
>  Timescity.com  
>  Times Internet Limited  
>  4th Floor, MPD Tower,  
>  DLF City Phase V, Opposite DLF Golf Course  
>  Gurgaon, Haryana 122002  
>  India  
>  Ph: 0124-4187000  
> 

**We request you to please provide the following information in your complaint:-**  

  * A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner for the purposes of the complaint.
  * Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed.
  * Identification of the material on our website that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity.
  * Your address, telephone number or e-mail address.
  * A statement that you have a good-faith belief that the information has been processed incorrectly or disclosed without authorization, as the case may be.
  * A statement, under penalty of perjury, that the information in the notice is accurate, and that the information being complained about belongs to you.

## Copyright Notice

Copyright © 2014 Timescity. All rights reserved.  
This Privacy Policy notification is subject to change at any time without any notice.
